Ta-da!
Let's all ring in the New Year together!
Thank you for your support this year
Let's pass the New Year together!
Debut in the city, debut in Furu is about to start!
Are you feeling happy?
It's almost over...
It's done, it's done, it's done, Colonel!
Gyoza Pan, thank you so much!
Maripo, thank you for 2023.
Ryan, it's countdown time.
Brothers and friends, Toshikatsuno.
And me, Yoshitsune Minamoto.
Let's all ring in the New Year together!
Debut for the coming debut for the going debut, it's starting!
Over there!
De-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de-de
Devil!
De-de-de-de-de-devil!
Kanai Devil!
Yay!
So, here we go
DeVille, DeVille, DeVille, DeVille, DeVille, DeVille, DeVille, DeVille, DeVille, DeVille
Tashikushi, Live Broadcast & Live Delivery Special
Ahhhh, it's really here again this year!
I look forward to this every year, don't you?
So, I've been looking forward to it every year, haven't I?
I've been living temporarily...
I want to make noise in Ghibli.
It's an experience I'll never get used to... and I'm sure Mayamatti is watching us.
I want to be a sound guy.
I didn't really feel it until just now... that it's really over today.
I was just starting to feel it... like I'm finally home...
I've been thinking about it for a while now... but I'm not sure if it's the same for me.
I'm not going to use a mirror...
How about you, Master?
Sapong, how are you doing? I'm nervous for the first time this year. Sarpon, how's it going?
I'm nervous for the first time!
That's what I've been thinking.
I'll be broadcasting it live on youtube too, of course!
I'm looking forward to your comments and I hope you'll join me on Rebuild Charge. I'll be commenting a lot.
Please share some of your comments with us.
Maybe it's not the Goddess of the house, but there's more... there's more...
There's more!
But, you know, there's that super-chat thing, too...
It's just like us, it's 23:36 or so in real time...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I wonder what they are going to do to make us laugh a lot.
I'm always laughing.
I'd like to laugh a lot.
You should go somewhere like that.
Buber... how about some seasoned dumpling buns?
I've lived my whole life without regret... so I'm cool... we'll be old women after this year.
I want to turn 24 this year.
I'll be 24 this year. - Really? That's great!
I'm looking forward to it!
I want to clean myself up!
Go home and boogie. It's open.
Do you have anything you want to do? Is there anything you want to do?
Well... maybe... have a drink.
We do this every year.
Like, "Wow, wow!
It's not really like Yoshizumi Mito, is it?
Someone is a big fan of Yoshizumi Mito, and he wants us to do it.
You mean as a guideline?
I don't know what you mean by "a big fan of Yoshizumi Mito.
I don't know what you mean.
Well, I'd like to do it, but it's not that easy.
I drank a glass of water just now and really enjoyed it.
It's the same clear water.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, I'm in the mood.
I'm a little drunk.
You're early. You're early.
You know, there are things you haven't done yet.
There's something you haven't done yet.
This is it, isn't it?
This is it.
Because I love soba.
So you want to eat New Year's Eve soba.
I want to eat it.
Actually...
My sister members who couldn't make it today...
They went to the location to get ingredients for New Year's Eve soba.
First of all, Hanamichi and Subieba are in the soba area.
Dekokun and Iwakadani picking vegetables for toppings
Harvesting vegetables for toppings
Maybe you mean tempura?
I don't understand what "harvesting vegetables for toppings" means!
That's difficult.
So you have a VTR of it?
Yes.
Let's take a look at it.
So... what I want is an impersonation of Kokun and a VCR.
I dug up some vegetables.
I don't know if I got the soba right, but take a look anyway.
They look so much alike!
Okay, now we're going to try our hand at making soba noodles.
Let's hear how enthusiastic you are!
I've been training my muscles for today.
I've been working on my arm strength.
How do you feel? How do you feel?
I lifted a plastic bottle.
I'm going to do what's called "bowl work".
It's to make it into one lump in the end.
The potting work is to make it into one lump in order to stretch it.
And from there, the process of stretching and cutting is called "potting".
Well, this is for your reference.
Today's soba is skin soba, skin soba.
Kanagawa Prefecture, skin-no-ken
Skin-no-ken skin rights
Okay.
I didn't know about that one.
What are the characteristics of skin conditioned buckwheat noodles?
What are the characteristics of skin-on-soba?
It smells like it's being cooked, or maybe it smells savory.
I love it every time!
By the way, I think you might be the best at training soba muscles.
Mr. Nakamura?
Me?
Mr. Kaya.
Yuna's muscle training is being tested.
Are you here?
She's here.
I'm only one member of the team, but I can't imagine how powerful they are.
Worry team!
I'm going to get lots of delicious vegetables.
I'll do my best.
Oh!
Oh, wow!
We got it!
Amazing! Refrain!
I got it!
I had some green onions on the side of my yard that I had left lying around.
It smells better than that.
Oh! Oh, good!
Next to the house, next to the house.
Go to the left.
There you are!
That's it.
Ha!
Oh! I got it!
Oh, great!
Higher up.
That's right.
Higher.
Oh, here it comes!
Nice.I got it!
I got it!
The purple one is a bit fluffier.
This one is more like a sizzle.
Sizzling!
I think it's thicker in the middle.
In that sense...
It's so close.
I'm looking at it with you!
That's great!
I don't think about it.
I'm not thinking anything.
Oh, it looks like a carrot.
Carrots!
Oh, my God!
That's unusual.
Wow! Wow!
Oh, they've turned color?
Good job, guys.
Give it a little jiggle. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
A little bit goes a long way.
It's stuck!
Come on.
Huh!
What?
Come on.
- Aah! Huh! Oh, great!
First vegetable harvest. Round 9 in progress.
Ouch. Ouch.
You're right.
Hang in there!
Fire!
I've got a special move!
I'm out!
That's what I'm talking about.
Oh, man.
Oh, man! It's so big! It's huge! It's so huge!
Now I'm going to cut up the green onions that will be everyone's topping!
I'm going to break them up into thin strips.
They're so crispy.
That's great!
It's a lot crisper than I thought it would be.
Wow, that was fast, fast, fast!
Good job! That's great.
Well, then, you're the lucky one who got this.
It's a forest of love.
Oh, right.
Forest of Love
There's one really big one.
It's a cat's paw, and it's doing great.
I want to be a cook someday.
Really?
Kaho is really good at it.
I mean, I hear she cooks a lot.
I hear she's making lots of things.
Don't you envy her?
I'll be mad tomorrow.
It's done!
Please eat it with a lot of buckwheat paste!
Whoever finds this is a rare find.
It's been a great year!
Thank you very much.
Ending
Thank you for watching!
Yuna, you're amazing!
Yuna, you can be a craftsman now!
I think I'll get on a buckwheat noodle shop.
Eh, thank you so much until now.
Light
It's light.
Come on!
That's it
Two sheets are done, so just pull it.
Two more times.I'll go two more times.
Come on.
Here's how to split it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Momentum.
The way to split it.
Oh!
And now... rotate it 180 degrees.
Oh, 180 degrees.
That's about right.
Hmm?
You mean like this.
Maybe it's 90 degrees.
No, no, no.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
If you cut in 1, 2, 3, then you cut in 1, 2, 3, and so on.
Heh.
Yes, it looks thin.
Oh, but you change it.
I couldn't cut this.
1, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, 2, 3, it's the way to split, it's the way to split, it's the way to split, it's the way to split
Split it, split it, split it, split it, split it, split it, split it, split it, split it.
Yes, yay!
So there's the one that everyone made.
First of all, Hanamichi soba, right?
Why are there thick noodles in it?
I was apologized for this before I came here today.
Before I came here today, she apologized to me, saying, "I'm sorry, I thought you would eat Miria-chan's soba.
He apologized for that too.
By the way, that Subie one looks good, but a little short.
But it's amazing how thinly it can be cut.
It's even.
And here's how to split it.
The way to split it is like this.
You can choose the thickness of the noodle.
It's kind of random.
It's like a baby store kind of thing.
The vegetable toppings are chopped green onion, grated radish, tempura cauliflower, and shaved carrot. The vegetable toppings are chopped green onion, grated radish, tempura cauliflower, and carrot kakiage.
It smells so good!
The grated daikon is so colorful!
Can I eat it?
Yes, you can!
Fat!
New!
It's brand-new.
Let's start with the flower arrangement.
Shall we?
Wow! What's this? It looks like a Kishimen!
Bon appétit!
It's stuck! It's stuck!
Hanamichi!
Do you like this?
I don't know...
It's good.
It has texture.
It's like...
It's like country buckwheat noodles.
Bon appétit!
I'd like to add the green onions that Emma and Yu cut up for me.
Red.
It's firm.
It's kind of...
Red.
It's like eating gum.
The texture is...
It's buckwheat, but it's firm.
Like udon noodles.
You might like it.
The green onion is so good!
Tempura looks good too
But it's so thick
It smells like buckwheat.
That's for sure!
This is a good idea!
I'm a barry cutter, and I'd like to try some. I'm Barry Cutter, and I'd like to talk a little bit.
Barry cutter.
I love green onions!
Oh, man!
Delicious!
It's from Subiya.
It's not in here!
Koi nobori!
I think it's gone.
Hey!
Can I look for it?
Daikon radish is delicious.
I love handmade soba noodles!
Want some?
Vegetables are terrible!
I don't know which ones are which!
Which one is it?
Which is it?
No, it's not...
They're not here.
They're sitting here eating.
It's like they're whispering.
Cauliflower.
I want some cauliflower.
Here you go.
Tempura.
Purple
Grated radish
Grated radish.
Delicious.
It came out fluffy!
All vegetables are sweet and delicious!
Vegetables are so good!
Fluffy cauliflower.
It's so good.
It's got so much flavor.
Carrots are the best!
What's this? what's this?
Everyone was very satisfied!
I was worried about it on the VTR, but when I actually ate it, it was so delicious!
Delicious!
It's so good!
You guys did a great job!
Thank you so much.
It's going fast.
I was afraid we wouldn't be able to have New Year's Eve soba today.
Yeah, it's great.
That's great.
Did you get the batcher?
Zadar's Yuhi...
I'm sorry, I'm just eating.
He wishes that 2024 will be a good year for all Devil members.
Thank you very much.
I really hope it will be a good year for Zadar as well.
I know.
I hope so.
I wonder what everyone is doing?
I wonder if they're eating toshikoshi soba (buckwheat noodles).
Ueno no Kami's place...
Has it already turned?
It has.
Master, they're eating normally.
He's eating a lot!
It's a counter, right?
It's really good.
I'm addicted to soba at Hanamichi.
These...
I love the harmony of the thick and thin noodles.
I love the harmony.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, this is good.
Delicious!
Thank you very much.
Let's get ready for the next corner. I'm going to go to the next corner.
I'd like to go to the next corner.
What's next?
Oh, my God, it's me, isn't it?
I'm going to sing a...
I wrote a song called "Toshikoshi no uta".
I wrote a song about Toshikoshi.
Not more than 8 minutes left.
Less than 8 minutes.
To the end of the year.
Oh, my God.
So fast.
It doesn't feel like the end of the year at all.
With this song.
With all of you
I'd like to count down
I'd like to do it.
I'll see you later.
Mariko, please.
Just a little longer.
Wait a little longer.
Idol-like
CM
And, and, and, and...
Yes! Well, I guess this is goodbye! Hello!
Oh no!
Only 5 minutes to go!
I've always wanted to sing over the New Year.
So, we talked about doing something like that this time, and after much deliberation, we came up with a song that goes "Zero" and "Boom" at the end.
I'd like to do it from now on.
I'm going to play it now, but surprisingly there's about a minute left.
This is the most nerve-wracking time.
I'm nervous.
But I'm listening to you... you've had a lot of vtrs.
Lamar.
Anyway, that soba was so good, it's in my mouth now.
I want to eat it now. I want to eat it now.
I'll definitely eat tempura later when I'm at the CM.
I want to taste it again slowly and more slowly.
And so, the year 2023 is almost over.
The last one.
Oh, my God!
Wait a minute!
Are you sure you're okay?
I really have to go.
Come on, come on.
Surprisingly, you can make it in time for something like this.
It's good to get out of here like this, isn't it?
It's fine.
Here we go!
This year is almost over.
Thank you, 2023. Thank you.
The new year will be here soon.
Happy new year to you, 2024!
Please subscribe to our channel.
Let's start the countdown!
La la la la la la countdown!
Let's countdown together!
♪ lalalalalalala, lalalalalala, lalalalalala, countdown ♪
Let's countdown!
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la countdown ♪
♪ La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la countdown ♪
Let's do it together.
Oh, no.
One minute to go.
My penquin.
Oh, my God.
That's amazing.
You're gonna do a guitar solo?
I'm gonna get a guitar solo.
Guitar solo.
Woo.
Oh, my God.
Oh, man. Oh, my God.
What do you mean?
Oh...
Ah!
Oh!
I want this!
I got my favorite snacks!
Thank you for watching!
I'll give you 20.
Here you go.
Okay.
Twenty.
Nineteen.
Eighteen.
9 9
One.
OH!
Happy New Dear!
Gacho Gacho Gacho Gacho
Happy New Dear
Gacho Gacho Gacho Digewon
Gacho Gacho Gacho Gacho
Shibuya Japan Encouragement SimulC enemy
Happy New Year!
I look forward to working with you!
I look forward to working with you.
Well, well, well...
Well, I don't know...
It was amazing, wasn't it?
Hamidoro.
I'm up!
I'm so proud.
That's the one I'm giving you.
Oh, really?
That's fun.
I gave it to him.
No, wait!
It's like tempura.
I gave it to you.
No, no, no.
Oh, my God.
It's beautiful.
Maybe it's those foreigners. Maybe those overseas people
I bet they're really excited.
I can't lose.
We can't lose.
It's so beautiful.
It's nice.
Well, well, well... That's why, isn't it?
Oh, no, no, no, no.
That was really great, wasn't it?
It was a lot of fun.
It was the first time.
After all...
So we had a Happy New Year.
It's been four years since we've been together.
I see.
We had a Canton dan concert.
One Canton dan concert.
Except for that one.
We're kind of in a funk right now.
In the studio.
There's a mood of celebration.
So happy.
We're in the most celebratory mood.
Happy New Year 2024!
Happy New Year!
Pappa pappa!
Pappapa!
It looks good on you, doesn't it?
I don't do it like this
Well, well, well...
Last year there was a movement to create a new hero in the DeVille.
Master, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm going to sit down.
I want to go to the flower stand.
I'll be right back...
I want to create a new hero in the Devil's Den, so...
I wanted to create a new hero in the Devil's house... so I asked for your ideas... but...
I'd like to create a new hero in the Devil's Den, and I've been asking for ideas from everyone. The design was designed by our hero himself, and we'd like you to take a look at it once more, please.
What's that sound?
What's with the long left hand and the right hand?
I've already done that... it's just that I want it to take shape.
I'm curious...
I want to make it a live-action film.
I want to make a live-action version of this movie and give birth to a hero who will make his debut in the true sense of the word.
So we've been working on it from various angles, and this time we've come up with this
I've been working on it from various angles, and I've made a little vtr, including an opening song.
I'm sure you'll like the scene with the cake on the cake.
Well then, everyone, please have a look.
Awww!
Oh, wow!
What?
That's it.
This is never gonna work.
Okay, okay.
I'm out.
Majida, Kaido, Garazin, Rockido.
I'm gonna cut the machine loose, go outside the speed limit.
Someone's calling for help.
Bad guys are beat bus. Don't get hurt.
Refreshing punch, cosmic energy
I'll give you a flower, a nightmare of recreation
Rayer, Rayer, Rayer, Kani-Mel Hero
Rayer, Rayer, Rayer, Kani-Mel Rayer
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
Ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma.
Wonderful.
I like it.
What did you think, frankly?
Well, frankly, I'm glad to see what this hand was all about.
I'm sure you're right.
I wonder if it was your partner's hand.
Was it your partner's hand?
I don't know yet, but...
I don't know yet.
I don't know. What?
That Kamen Liar has come to this studio!
What?
That's amazing!
That's amazing.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
That's great.
Thank you. Thank you.
What?
That's what I'm talking about.
He doesn't speak the language.
Is it like Mensa?
Yes.
Ng...
People who had it before could speak.
But after it...
I see.
But instead, it defeats evil, right?
You look weak.
He looks so weak.
That's for sure.
High cut.
Kitchen.
I really don't like this flower stuck in his head.
What is this?
It's so tacky.
I want this flower.
You said you cared about flowers.
If I saw it as an illustration...
I'm sure there's a grilled chicken stick in it.
It was a flower.
A flower.Flowers
Do you have a question for Ryer?
Yes, I do.
How long does it take for a masked liar to become a real person?
It's a mask now.
Third stage.
Big brother.
About three months?
About three years.
Wow!
It's a tough lesson.
I see.
My shoulder is like this.
Oh, my God.
I can't turn my neck.
You must have slept wrong.
You slept wrong.
That's great.
That's what this corner is for.
It's not a gesture corner, but...
If you have any questions or comments, I'll be happy to answer them.
I'll be happy to answer them.
Is this your partner's hand?
That's...
It's black.
I see.
I knew it.
It's like your partner's hand and that hand are clasping each other
Oh!
So it's kind of emo.
I see.
So it has a meaning.
And this belt bark is really nostalgic.
I don't know.
Peace.
Is it a symbol?
You're aiming for peace, aren't you? So you're aiming for peace.
I see.
Violence is no good, right?
It's a no-no, after all.
Do you have any special moves?
I'm curious.
Not at all.
Earth's moisture.
Your flowers are all messed up.
Oh, so you draw flowers, right?
I've got a question for you.
What do you usually do, Mr. Riger?
Oh.
Yes, sir.
Construction site? Oh, you do that.
He's so sweet. He's so Japanese. He's so sweet.
Do you have any special moves you've learned recently? No different than the one you just did.
What kind of punch is the Sawayaka Punch?
The Sawayaka Punch.
The run-up.
It's certainly refreshing.
How about a 2-D kick?
Two-dimensional.
Oh, wow.
But it's kind of kicking.
My feet hurt.
Two dimensional
I'm not sure I'd like this.
I like it.
You're right, the chest plate is thin.
It's true.
Is it a charm that her skirt is too short? I mean...
Yes, it is.
I'll work on it from now on.
Well, well, well.
Well then...
Is it okay like this?
Ah! Like your relationship with Shingo-kun? Ah! Like your relationship with Mr. Shingo.
He's shaking hands with his partner.
It was a bit of a mystery, wasn't it?
I don't know. I don't know myself and I don't know you.
I don't know.
So it's going to become clear from now on.
It's a great storyline, isn't it?
A friend at heart, I guess.
Friends of the heart, definitely.
So, it's going to be 2020, right?
I'm sure it's going to be revealed in earnest this spring.
Is this going to be a series?
I'd like to see it.
I see.
Rumor has it that there may be a nationwide series.
What's it about?
I know what it is.
Ryan, I don't know.
Rumor.
Like, everyone in the country shaking hands with me.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Like, little kids.
I'm gonna shake hands with all the little kids in the country.
I'll have all the little kids in the country shake hands with me.
No, no, no, no, don't do that.
Don't do it. It's scary.
Pervert-consciousness.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
Is it time to go home?
Oh, it's glowing.
There's a timer, isn't there?
Manual.
You have two timers.
Two timers. Double standby.
So that one glows, too.
It's like you're waking up from a really bad night's sleep.
There's a lot of alarms. The alarms are going off like crazy.
Charisma's not so good if you don't water her.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
See you later, Ryan.
Thank you for your time.
Thank you.
He's smiling, he's smiling.
I'm not nauseous at that moment.
You're laughing.
Let's go again.
Bye-bye, bye-bye, bye-bye.
Thank you.
Okay.
That's it. I'm not nauseous.
You should go.
I think you should go.
That didn't mean anything.
It didn't mean anything.
What was that?
That's great camera work.
Oh, my God.
Well, well, well.
Hey, hey, hey, Master.
I was wondering if we could move on to the next one.
Oh, no.
What's next?
Next... we're all going to...
The project we all tried...
Last year.
We did it, didn't we?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
By the way, what did we all do?
All of us.
We're going to go to Halimen Ryan's house.
Otaku-homa.
Otaku Houma
Bugs. Bug.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no...
It's been exciting. It's been exciting.
I can't wait to see what he can do in the future.
Next is TVK's 51st anniversary 51 times long rope challenge.
Last year was TVK's 50th anniversary, and this year is their 51st anniversary.
For our 50th anniversary we did a 50 meter run together and the master ran a 50 km marathon.
I was going to do 51 kilometers this year, but my knee got worse, so I'm sorry, I'll do 52 kilometers next year.
I'm sorry but I'll do it next year. 52 kilometers.
I'm sorry, I've been worrying a lot about you.
I'm sorry, I've been worrying a lot.
Let's watch the VTR.
Oh, he's doing it! She's doing it!
Harumi, stay here for a minute.
Okay, come on!
Come on!
She won't stay!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, hey, hey.
Hey! There, too!
There, too! There, too!
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Hey! Hey!
Hey! I wanna go!
Hey! I can go, I can go, I can go!
Nice try!
You can do it!
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it!
I can go, I can go, I can go!
I'm going for it!
I'm going for 50!
Okay.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Aah!
It's okay.
Ten!
Forty more!
And the guardians, they're here, too.
Just in case.
I know you're probably thinking right now when you see this.
Skip in a row.
Three, two, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Yeah!
Yes!
I did it anyway!
Twelve!
Well done, guys.
You can't do 40 more!
It's impossible!
Looking good, looking good.
I won't bail out for once.
It's not so bad.
I'm going around with this one.
No?
Oh, no.
It's not very steady, is it?
Suddenly there's oxygen.
What if next time...
We're down to about 10 people now.
There, there, that's the plan!
I mean, let's start the next one with 10.
For now.
Here they come!
You're so sweet.
That was fast.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Ready?
We're gonna do a real count here.
Yes, sir.Yes, sir.
Here we go.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15!
Fourteen! Yes!
That's good, that's good!
Next, 15!
Fifteen times to start.
Twenty-two, 23, 24, 25!
What's up?
We're taking turns.
Is he coming?
He's coming.
Doctor's stop.
General.
Take a break.
You.
28, 29, 30, 31, 32, 33, 34, 35, 36, 37, 38, 39, 38!
Gan jurisdictions. Yes, yes, gdzie.
[?
hesitate Hey, you know, that thing now, that completely
I don't need that laugh anymore.
anime
Professor.
I thought about it pretty fast.
Seino
Forty-one.
Forty-two.
50 50
Aaaaah!
Yay!
So close!
Just... 1.5 more!
- So close! So close! So close! So close!
Next time...
- Let's go for it! Please! Ready!
39 40 41 42
43 44 45
46 47 48
49 50 40 Yay!
- Yeah! Yeah! Yeah!
Yeah!
me
Oh, no!
Well, now that we've accomplished our mission, let's end on that note, shall we? Happy 51st anniversary, tvk!
Yo!
Yeah, yeah, yeah...
Yay, yay, yay!
Yay!
Anyway, the vtr is edited, so it took me quite a while to get there.
I really want to do 50 times, but the sun is setting and it's getting colder and colder...
I decided to change the strategy and went with the postponement strategy.
Master, you've been running like a demon.
I'm so scared when his name comes in.
I'm afraid to get my name in there.
I'm glad you're here... is your athletic ability being questioned?
I'm not sure if it's all right... but I've been writing about her athletic skills... and telling her to stop.
I'm sure it depends on the distance, but this is different... I heard the legend of Balikata from him.
I heard the legend of the ballet, and he said, "We had a ballet class, and we had to do it like this, and when we did it like this, the ball came out in this spot.
On the other hand, it was really good. It came out like a spawn.
It's not so easy to be a comedian.
They said they didn't need to laugh, but it was pretty good.
Next year is our 52nd anniversary, and I'd like to do something else in connection with the 52nd.
Now I would like to go to the next corner.
The debut of "Daikanai" to be held on March 31st at the Kanagawa Kenmin Hall, and all the goods for the event are now available! The debut of the show will be held on March 31st at the Kanagawa Prefectural Hall, and we've got all the goods for it!
Let's start from here.
This way?
Sakosh!
So cute!
What language?
"Succoshes.
They're all the rage these days.
It's easy to use for live performances.
You can write on it.
You don't know it.
I just found out about it, didn't I?
It holds a lot more than you'd think.
There's a tote bag and a pouch.
And the mugs are cute.
Here's a mug.
It has the same pattern as our hats.
And this time...
There's a mountain in Kanagawa prefecture called Mt.
There is a mountain in Kanagawa prefecture called Mt.
Fuji Rock Festival
Fuji Rock Festival at the foot of the mountain.
I thought it would be fun to have a rock festival like that.
I wrote a song about it.
I also took the liberty of making T-shirts.
I thought, "If you call it a festival, it's a T-shirt.
So I made one T-shirt.
I wore it by myself and smiled.
It seems that some of you are asking for it.
I made one of those T-shirts and wore it by myself and smiled.
I'm pleased to announce that we are now officially selling them.
You can only get it here!
I'm sure you'll love it!
It doesn't look like this rock festival exists.
It's a fictional rock festival.
It would be nice if we could.
And...And...
Here is everyone's favorite acrylic stand!
Here it is!
It's in a special pose, though.
Amazing!
I hope you can get all of them.
Some of you look like Shae.
I've been asked to strike a funny pose.
Since we're here...
They're all like that, aren't they?
And this one has an actor.
And this is
Fontainebleau and Slap.
What language?
Is it Japanese? Is it English? French?
Fontainebleau & Slap
Isn't this a rare item?
Don't start chewing.
Fon Tabou and Slap.
Pong.
Phone call.
You're posing for the phone.
Pow.
Your accent is a little...
You're too native. I can't hear you.
This is what it is, isn't it?
You know, the one you put in your cell phone and wear around your neck?
What's it called?
Pon.
What's that on your phone? Tuck it in.
You put it in and hang it from your neck.
That's right.
Is there a better way to say it?
It's all the rage these days.
You put something inside?
You put it between the phone and the case, and then you slap it around your neck.Slap it around your neck between your phone and case.
Then you can see it.
And what a fine variety it is, too!
It's a scene on the reverse side.
The front side is a picture of you.
The back side is a picture of the creatures that you drew at the debut of the museum.
The picture on the back is a picture of the creatures that you drew for the debut of the museum.
It's so nice!
That's what I was thinking.
I drew everyone's face.
It's so rare!
I want this!
What's this?
It's now on sale at TVK Mall!
This is a made-to-order item, so you can't buy it at the venue.
but if you buy it at TVK Mall and spend more than 10,000 yen
and the price is over 10,000 yen, you will get an original poster as a special offer.
An original poster is also included.
I hope you all can get a variety of posters.
If you can, Master, this is a good one.
What's this?
What is it?
Pontab.
Ponta Band Tharp.
That's good, isn't it?
I bought a complete box of acrylic stands.
I'll get a poster for myself.
Yay!
I knew it!
There is a complete box?
Yes, there is.
Okay, Master, let's move on.
Why did you get up?
Gundam.
The merchandise is for everyone to buy. The idea is that everyone gets to buy the goods.
Here is the next corner!
Who will be the MVP of the museum's Devil's 2023?
MVP
Did you fill out the questionnaire in advance?
I did.
Who do you think has done the best in 23 years in terms of DeVille?
And what was the most memorable event or word? Questionnaire
I asked each of you to write your answers.
I'd like to announce them now.
The person who gets the most votes will be the MVP.
It may or may not be a good thing.
Maybe not.
Yes, yes, yes.
Okay, then.
Masasic.
So you all wrote.
I did.
It's nice to have an MVP, isn't it?
It was a tough decision.
Well, let's start with
I'll start with Billiketu.
Billiketz.
Second from the bottom.
I'll start with the second one.
I don't know what "Birikketsu" means.
It means that you didn't get any votes.
The person with the fewest votes...
Okay, last one.
I'll leave the first one and the last one.
I'll start with the second one.
There were three people who received two votes.
First of all, Subie.
She worked hard 24 hours a day, every day, doing everything she could, and it was amazing.
You mean Subie.
Yes, that's right.
It's not a show or anything.
It's a life of its own. I'll take that as a yes.
In a year.
In our survey.
If you're a member of Ebichu...
It's okay if it's not about the show.
I see.
So it's 24 hours a day now.
Well, that's a good thing.
I was afraid of the airplane road when I was on a live expedition, but I did my best to get on it.
He's cute.
Like that.
So that's the kind of MVP you're looking for.
Anything goes, right?
And next.
Sawapon.
He's ranked in.
I don't know who this is.
I was singing when I was BFF.
The sesner sound is impressive.
There?
You did it.
Thank you very much.
And for having the biggest smile on your master's buckeye.
If you're smiling, you're doing great.
Please don't. It's like a job.
I was just trying to be nice.
Master.
The owner took the 51st challenge.
Mr. Sawapon and I were saying that it might be better this way.
Mr. Sawapon and I were talking about how we should do it.
I'll go next time. I'm not saying there was a gag or anything.
He worked so hard, he even went so far as to put a doctor's stop to it.
I'm sure they'll be fine.
And then there were three votes for Ganbadanin!
I've never done this before, but I've been trying so hard to keep up with them.
Gandanifire was "I can't talk." And of all the younger sisters, she was just as ready to make her debut as Mirei.
And she was just as ready to make her debut as Mirei. He was able to shift gears for his debut.
Next, Master, when we played in New Zealand, I was in an absolute pinch because I had a bad throat condition and all the rehearsals were back to back.
I was so happy that you came next to me and worried about me when I was so depressed.
On the day of the show, he told me how I should do it when I had difficulty speaking.
I think it must have been Subie.
Maybe it's Sue.
Gambandani.
Gambadanny.
He wasn't feeling well.
Yeah, Gambandani wasn't feeling well.
That's a great compliment.
Heh.
That's not a nice thing to say.
That has nothing to do with it.
It's a good story.
Okay, first place.
I'm curious about this.
The master's spell is gone
For those of you who like Harriott...
Ron Weasley's lickspittle
There's no spell to bring it to a boil
It was indeed Master Weasley
by saying that he had no idea what he was doing.
That was amazing.
It was shocking, wasn't it?
I said "no more" a lot.
I don't say it often.
I don't say it very often.
So that's the one who got three votes.
That leaves us with four votes and one vote.
And the one who got one vote.
Can you explain?
I'd like to know one vote.
I'll go now.
Mr. Main.
You're the main staff member, aren't you?
Mr. Staff.
Mr. Staff. Staff.
Wow!
Wow.
This is Nussy.
Not at all appropriate for the New Year?
Yes, it is!
Watch out, everybody!
I was in Cannadaville.
What kind of bandit is this?
Can I tell you why?
When we went to the devil's den, I did 100 montages before the meeting.
Some of them I didn't understand.
But he did 100 of them, and he was amazing.
He did.
Well, well, well.
It took you five minutes.
Oh, yeah.
Is that you? Could it be...
It's me.
Then Nussy has my vote.
I learned a lot.
And now I'd like to announce the MVP.
Please announce the MVP.
The MVP is...
Who is it?
Shohei Otani!
I knew it!
I knew it! Shohei Otani!
The MVP.
I guess I'll be early.
That's a lie.
It's not a lie, but it's true.
I'm really going to announce it.
I'll announce it.
We got four votes.
We got it.
Balicata!
Oh, my God! Wow!
But I don't know...
I've never done this before, but I'm trying my best to keep up with it.
I mean, it's only been a year since I started working here.
He was doing his best.
And there was also someone who wrote that the entomophagy was bad.
I don't know who it was, but...
But he was eating it.
Or something like that.
Barikata.
This is also one of the Devil's buzzwords, "balikata.
There are many variations.
But I like the version served with balikata ramen the best.
Yes, yes, yes.
So...
That MVP is Balikata!
Congratulations!
That means Shohei Otani and Balikata, right?
That's right.
So it looks like there are VTRs of Balikata's various activities.
Let's take a look at one of them.
Here's Balikata!
Bon appétit!
We have prepared a New Year's gift for the mvp winners, Balikata and Ine Nakamura.
The jbl Tour Pro Two, the Frankship model of completely wireless earbuds!
The world's first smart charging case with touch screen and evolved noise canceling performance.
It is a wireless earphone that has won all kinds of awards!
Amazing.
It's a balicata.
Here's the master.
Can I show you the actual product?
It's really nice.
Oh, there's something on the screen.
Wow!
A lot of information is coming out, isn't it?
It's coming up.
Does this mean I can get hair clippers?
You can get it.You can have it.
Congratulations, Balikata.
By the way, I didn't get a single vote for dumpling bread.
Who? Why?
I'm glad you said that.
It's funny, you didn't get one. Let's work hard this year.
Let's work hard this year.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes.
So, what do you think?
I just got a present for the balikbayans.
What a surprise! The museum devils are giving out New Year's presents to our viewers as well!
Thank you very much!
I would like you to look at the vtr first to see what you can get, and here is the gift for our viewers
Two winners of the jbl swar pro 2 that we mentioned earlier Wireless headphones that are even lighter and more comfortable to wear, but still have powerful bass
jbl tune 770 nc, one of each color for a total of four winners
and jbl's portable bluetooth speakers, condensing the jbl sound into the size of a plastic bottle.
Flip 6
Pulse 5, which emits 360-degree sound and 60,000 colors of light
The body-shaped design of the Clip 4 is perfect for outdoor use.
We are giving away one of each of these items to one lucky winner. Please fill out the form on the program's homepage.
We are looking forward to hearing from you!
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
This is it. Nice and luxurious.
And we also use one of these, right? Yes, we have one of these. The previous model.
I think it's really convenient to have bluetooth speakers.
I've got them right here, can I play a little music now?
Start the music!
Oh, is he coming?
Seimaru!
Oh, no, I've lost my mind!
The phone's ringing.
The phone's ringing!
Oh, no.
That's what I'm talking about. That's what I'm talking about.
Is the phone gonna ring?
Can you make it? Is it gonna work?
That's what I'm talking about.
The phone's gonna ring.
Oh, here it comes!
Devil!
It's a commercial!
Commercial!
Yes, it's like this, and it sounds great, too.
Compact and cute.
I think it's very good, and I want to get one too!
You can apply for it by selecting the product you want from the website dedicated to this program.
Please choose your desired product from the website dedicated to the program and apply for it!
So, now that that's out of the way, let's get back to the show!
I'll ask the Chief to join us today.
Yes, a Scorsabo, what are your impressions of the show so far?
What are your thoughts on the show so far?
Buss...
Okay, so...
Watch out, watch out, watch out!
I'm sure it'll come out after it's out of alignment.
So now...
We're finally in the last half of the show...
To Cervon...
I've already given you a challenge... for the New Year's Eve special.
Yes, that's right... every year on December 12, they announce the Kanji character for this year, right?
They did it last year, didn't they?
That's right, and I was told to be the first to predict this year's winner.
Oh, the one for this year.
That's right.
December 2024, so that's about a year from now.
I've been thinking about it.
Yes.
I wonder if I'll be right. It would be nice if I'm right.
The odds are staggering. I'd like to win it if I win this.
I'd like to win it if I win it.
Here's what you get.
A million!
You don't know what it is?
One million.
A million.
But the Kanji character is...
How are you going to announce the kanji?
That's right.
I'm going to write them in a certain way during the live broadcast.
But before that, I've practiced in advance.
Practice
I have a VTR of the practice, so please take a look at it.
Please watch it.
Please go ahead.
Hi, I'm Saton.
Oh, my God.
Well...
I'm dressed like this.
I was really looking forward to today.
Yes, I was.
Well...
Kakizome, if you call it that...
It's a bit artistic, isn't it?
If I say "art," it's me.
When I say art, I mean me
If I say "art," well, that's me.
I'm thinking of writing in an artistic way.
Yes, sir.
Poke
Hook.
huh?
what
a
e
Ha Ha!
Please subscribe to our channel!
This is... The prize.
I won!
And the biggest one of all...
Baseball.
There was the World Baseball Classic.
There was a World Baseball Classic?
I'm sorry, I'm not sure how to pronounce it.
The locals say "Baseball Classic.
Well, there was the World Baseball Classic.
I'll go then.
Ha!
Yo! Oh!
Oh, good, good, good, good, good.
Ho!
There you go.
Here you go.
May I have a word?
This is written "Nakajima Raiya", right?
Yes, it is.
I'll make it work.
I'll make it work from here.
It'll be quick.
Here it is! It's done!
I'll make you cry! I'll make you cry!
I'll make it look good.
I'll start from here.
Well, it's early.
No, it's really good.
It's very good.
It's just, um...
I can't write Ebisu. I can't write Ebisu.
I can't write Ebisu.
I can't write Evinor either.
I used to work part-time at Ebiner.
but even I can't write prawns!
Isn't it hard to write "ebi"?
I worked part-time at an ebinner, but...
Not shrimp!
I can't even write "shrimp"!
Isn't it hard to write "prawn"?
Don't be completely wrong!
Sei!
I got it!
Oh!
I'm sorry.
Is everything okay?
That's it, isn't it?
That Kibu Tison is coming later.
The little one?
Oh, no, no, no, no!
Screw this on.
Here...
Nice sea, isn't it? This is...
It's a nice sea, isn't it?
Question B.
But I feel like I'm supposed to let it die.
Personally...
Like a fire.
That means "B" of "shrimp" is only used for "Bi".
That means the "B" in shrimp is only used for "Bi".
That means only "B" in "shrimp" is used for "Bi".
It's done!
Shrimp
Shrimp Junior High School
The "B" in shrimp...
I'm going to get in trouble.
I'm going to get in trouble for this. This is going to piss me off.
I used to work part-time at Ebiner.
I can't even write "shrimp"!
Shrimps are hard to write, aren't they?
That's not it.
So, I'll do my best for the show.
I'm going to do my best in the show. It's going to be great!
I'll write it!
Please write it down.
Well, well, well, well, well...
That's how it goes
That's why...
Here it is.
A giant block of paper.
I've never seen anything like it.
This is how you write on it.
What's that?
I don't get it.
What was that?
It's like "bya"!
What do you mean?
You really scared me just now.
It's too technical.
I thought you did it.
I thought it was the first brush in TV history.
Oh, my God.
Right here in front of Mr. Rhea's waiting room.
I think he's on the air.
Please relay the news.
Who is it?
Hey, hey, hey... you forgot about me.
My name is Envil Nakakurobiru, and it's Envil New Year's Eve!
You're a character, this Enville.
We're here in front of your waiting room, Mr. Raia.
I'll knock on the door right away. I'll knock on the door as soon as I can.
Knock-knock, knock-knock, Mr. Rhea, how are we looking?
It's looking good.
By the way, prawns are not prawns in prawns are not prawns in prawns are not prawns in prawns
I'm sorry, I'm really sorry, but I can do it now.
I'm back.
I'm sure you're all looking forward to it.
I'm looking forward to seeing you all... like this.
Evil Evil Evil Evil Evil Evil Evil Evil Evil Evil Evil Evil Evil Evil Evil
What is your goal for this year?
My goal is to talk a lot.
I'm going to try to talk a lot with a lot of people.
It's out already!
I wonder if she's ready to go.
I wonder if she's ready.
I'm pretty much ready.
By the way, does anyone in the studio have anything to say to Mr. Rhea?
Well, I'd like you to do your best.
Do your best so I don't get the wrong feeling.
Do your best.
Thank you.
You're showing through.
It's showing.
You're showing.
I missed it.
I'll take you back to the studio.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's Evil.
You were pretty much in full view.
All kinds of things.
So, Master...
Please give a shout out to Sarpon, who is going to do a giant hang-dyeing after this.
It's an amazing work of art!
I'll be counting on you.
Excuse me.
Oh! Oh!
Cool.
Sensei.
I'm going to make soba now.
No, no, no.
You saw the VCR.
This is it.
I'm looking forward to working with you.
How are you feeling about it?
Well, I've been trying to draw Ebisu.
I hope to draw good characters.
It was amazing, wasn't it, how the beauty of the shrimp's handwriting was totally different?
I'm sorry.
It was all art.
So, you have already decided on a character in your mind?
Yes, I have already made up my mind.
Well then, please, sir.
I'm looking forward to it.
Excuse me.
That's great!
The one kanji character for the year 2024 is...
Wow!
What is it?
Okay, I'll go.
Oh!
Art.
Oh, my God.
Ooh!
No hesitation
Ha!
That's great.
You okay?
Ha!
What do you mean? What does that mean?
What's going to happen?
Meow.
what is it?
what?
what what what
Uh...
Ah!
It's done!
Oh, it's a painting of the name of the work.
I see.
There was no hesitation.
Very artistic!
Oh, my God!
Great, why is the name of the work painted here, Mr. Kikuchi?
Yes, I knew it... next year, not next year, but this year.
Do you know what's going to happen this year?
Shihpei is changing.
Oh, yes, the judging.
And you know, last year was a little darker than last year's ZE!
Why do you think we're going for a revolution this time?
I'm going for it.
I'm going for it really hard.
Something revolutionary, something new.
Yes, something new.
I thought it would happen.
I was hoping that it would happen.
Easy.
Well, well, well, well...
By the way, the questions from the audience...
I'm impressed by what you've done, Mr. Sharpe, for example.
They say that fans look for guesses, but what are your impressions of your fans? I don't know if this is relevant, but I'd love to have some, Millie, I love you.
Thank you very much for your time.
I guess I'm just saying that your fans are like you... full of energy.
I see.
I see... that's how it is... that's how it is.
You have this look?You had this outfit?
Yes. Shall I read another one?
The last one? Last?
Uh, something with a cross in it.
If you could add any word to your level name, like dumpling buns became fresh dumpling buns, what would you add?
Wait, that was 20 seconds. We have to start a revolution.
But maybe in the future...
Master...
It's over.
You guys
And Shihan University...